<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PizzaRecipes</string>

    <string name="pizza_1_name">Next level Margherita  pizza</string>
    <string name="pizza_1_description">Forget takeaways – you can’t beat a homemade Margherita pizza topped with fresh tomato sauce and melted cheese. Here\'s how to master this everyday classic…</string>
    <string name="pizza_1_recipe">TEP 1\n" +
            "First, make the dough. Tip the flour into a bowl and add 300ml tepid water. Mix together and set aside at room temperature for 1 hr. Dissolve the yeast in 2 tbsp water and mix this and 15g of salt through the dough. Cover with cling film and leave somewhere warm to double in size for a few hours. For a sourer flavour, leave in the fridge for at least 8 hrs and up to 24 hrs – the longer you leave it the sourer it will be.\n" +
            "\n" +
            "STEP 2\n" +
            "When the dough is ready, tip it onto a lightly floured surface and divide into four. Roll into balls and leave to rest, covered with a tea towel or cling film for another hour.\n" +
            "\n" +
            "STEP 3\n" +
            "Now make the tomato sauce. Drain some of the juice from the can and tip the rest into a bowl with the olive oil, oregano and a generous pinch of salt, then either scrunch everything together with your fingers for a chunky sauce or blitz with a stick blender if you want it smooth. Tie the basil stalks together, bruise with the back of a knife and place in the sauce. Leave the sauce at room temperature until needed.\n" +
            "\n" +
            "STEP 4\n" +
            "To make the pizza, heat a grill to its highest setting and get a heavy frying pan. On a floured surface push and stretch one of the balls of dough out into a circle roughly the same size as the frying pan. Slip the round onto a floured baking sheet and top with a quarter of the sauce, a scattering of cheese, a few basil leaves and a quarter of the mozzarella.\n" +
            "\n" +
            "STEP 5\n" +
            "Get the pan very hot and carefully slide the pizza onto it. Cook for 2 mins, then put the pan under the grill for another 2 mins until the sides are puffed up and the cheese has melted. Lift onto a board, drizzle with a little olive oil if you like, then cut into wedges and serve while you make the next one.</string>

    <string name="pizza_2_name">Caramelised onion &amp; goat’s cheese pizza</string>
    <string name="pizza_2_description">Make a veggie pizza that\'s healthy and low-fat instead of ordering a takeaway. This easy recipe uses goat\'s cheese for tang while the onions give it sweetness</string>
    <string name="pizza_2_recipe">STEP 1\n" +
            "Heat oven to 220C/200C fan/gas 7. Tip the flour into a mixer with a dough hook, or a bowl. Add the yeast, salt, oil and just under 100ml warm water then mix to a soft dough. Knead in the food mixer for about 5 mins, but if making this by hand, tip onto a work surface and knead for about 10 mins. The dough is sticky, but try not to add too much extra flour. Leave in the bowl and cover with a tea towel while you make the topping. There is no need to let the dough prove for a specific time – just let it sit while you get on with the next step.\n" +
            "\n" +
            "STEP 2\n" +
            "Tip the onions into a non-stick wok and add the oil, 4 tbsp water and balsamic vinegar. Cover with a saucepan lid that sits inside the pan to help the onions soften, then cook for 15 mins, stirring about 3 times and replacing the lid quickly so as not to lose too much moisture. After the time is up, the onions should be golden and all the liquid gone. Tip onto a plate. Add the spinach and garlic to the pan and stir-fry until the spinach has wilted.\n" +
            "\n" +
            "STEP 3\n" +
            "Take the dough from the bowl and cut in half with an oiled knife, then press each piece into a 25-15 cm oval on a large greased baking sheet with oiled hands. Don’t knead the dough first otherwise it will be too elastic and it will keep shrinking back.\n" +
            "\n" +
            "STEP 4\n" +
            "Spread with the spinach followed by the onions, then dot with the cheese and scatter with the olives, thyme and sunflower seeds. Bake for 15 mins until golden and the base is cooked through.</string>

    <string name="pizza_3_name">Caramelised onion &amp; goat’s cheese pizza</string>
    <string name="pizza_3_description">Make a veggie pizza that\'s healthy and low-fat instead of ordering a takeaway. This easy recipe uses goat\'s cheese for tang while the onions give it sweetness</string>

    <string name="pizza_4_name">Caramelised onion &amp; goat’s cheese pizza</string>
    <string name="pizza_4_description">Make a veggie pizza that\'s healthy and low-fat instead of ordering a takeaway. This easy recipe uses goat\'s cheese for tang while the onions give it sweetness</string>

    <string name="pizza_5_name">Caramelised onion &amp; goat’s cheese pizza</string>
    <string name="pizza_5_description">Make a veggie pizza that\'s healthy and low-fat instead of ordering a takeaway. This easy recipe uses goat\'s cheese for tang while the onions give it sweetness</string>

    <string name="pizza_6_name">Caramelised onion &amp; goat’s cheese pizza</string>
    <string name="pizza_6_description">Make a veggie pizza that\'s healthy and low-fat instead of ordering a takeaway. This easy recipe uses goat\'s cheese for tang while the onions give it sweetness</string>

    <string name="pizza_7_name">Caramelised onion &amp; goat’s cheese pizza</string>
    <string name="pizza_7_description">Make a veggie pizza that\'s healthy and low-fat instead of ordering a takeaway. This easy recipe uses goat\'s cheese for tang while the onions give it sweetness</string>

    <string name="pizza_8_name">Caramelised onion &amp; goat’s cheese pizza</string>
    <string name="pizza_8_description">Make a veggie pizza that\'s healthy and low-fat instead of ordering a takeaway. This easy recipe uses goat\'s cheese for tang while the onions give it sweetness</string>

    <string name="pizza_9_name">Caramelised onion &amp; goat’s cheese pizza</string>
    <string name="pizza_9_description">Make a veggie pizza that\'s healthy and low-fat instead of ordering a takeaway. This easy recipe uses goat\'s cheese for tang while the onions give it sweetness</string>

    <string name="pizza_10_name">Caramelised onion &amp; goat’s cheese pizza</string>
    <string name="pizza_10_description">Make a veggie pizza that\'s healthy and low-fat instead of ordering a takeaway. This easy recipe uses goat\'s cheese for tang while the onions give it sweetness</string>

</resources>